I'll always be with you, and I'll always be with you
Everything will change, everything will change
There's a smile on your lips
With you, with you, with you
If you love me, if you love me,
I'll become a person with a heart
I don't want to have a chance to be happy
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
If you experiment with the machine, it's a big problem
We broke into a world with a lot of work
I don't even know where this is
I don't even know how to return to the world
I didn't get bored
It seems that the family of adults has become friends
There was fun in this world together
I'm going to have fun
Hah!
It's good, isn't it?
Ah!
The film!
Your parents are you?
Is it a serious attack?
I think it's a big one!
It's amazing.
Oh no!
What's this?
I just got to play.
You want to play with us?
I'm really happy.
Are these your secret keys?
I'd like to play with you.
It's my secret keys.
Oh, no!
Huh? Is it a phone?
Shut up!
I don't know.
Really?
The phone was on the right.
I was able to see it from the other side.
Right?
I really didn't know that.
My mother told me to see it on the phone.
Oh, no.
What?
What was that phone called?
I was able to see it on the phone.
But it was a girl.
What?
It was Leo.
I didn't know that it was a phone call.
I was able to see it on the phone.
I see.
I don't know what it was.
Ah! That's it!
Oh!
I can't see it!
I know.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
I see.
I didn't know that it was a phone call.
My mother and I didn't know that it was a phone call.
I see.
I think it's because I think it's a phone call.
It might have been way more than the day after when you got in the car.
It might have been that moment.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
Huh?
Um, hello?
Hello?
What's wrong? Why don't you come?
Um, I'm waiting for you.
Just...
Um, you're...
I'm Hime from the castle of Almajiro.
Hime? You're not Babo-sama?
Babo?
I'm Yoreishi of Umogadani.
I'm Ueiba. I'm Ueiba from Shikata.
Huh?
Oh, hello? Hello?
Hello?
Um, I feel like I've heard from somewhere.
Did you hear me?
Did you talk to me?
You're Hime-sama from the castle.
Hime-sama?
I heard you came to the castle.
Did you hear me from the castle?
Um, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
But the castle is beautiful.
What's wrong?
What's the problem?
Let's get out of the castle.
Hey, Hime-sama!
Let's get out of here.
Oh, Mr. Yoseo.
I wonder if there's a problem in the castle.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Oh, Mr. Yoyoshi.
Did you find a good promise to be in the castle?
I'm sorry.
Really?
I really wanted to see you.
Ueiba, I believe in you.
Really?
I'm also interested in you.
Hime-sama.
I want to see you.
Hey, where did you come from?
Do you know where you came from?
I went to the castle of Armajiro.
But where did you come from?
Let's listen to each other once in a while.
That's right.
I don't know.
Yes.
Do you know?
Armajiro's castle is a castle.
It's the castle of Armajiro.
It's the castle of Ryoryoshi.
And where did you come from?
I wanted to take it.
But it's the castle of Armajiro.
I want to see you.
Yay!
It's the castle of Armajiro.
I'm going to take a good look at the opponent.
Ueiba.
Yes.
Do you know about Roku's father?
He's quite famous.
If you talk about him,
he's quite famous.
He's quite famous.
Yay!
This is the capital of the Mongolia.
What?
It's the capital of the Mongolia.
Look! There are many of the Dokutsu.
The capital of the father.
This is the capital of the father.
That's right.
Yay!
I'm glad you brought your friends today.
Roku...
My name is Oba.
I'm Ueiba.
My name is Okaida.
I was born in Okara.
Okara.
So, what should I do?
Um, I thought there was a special place behind Almajiro.
What was that place?
It was a famous place, so it was connected to the house.
It looks like it was a place where the parents lived.
I see, I see. It's a place where you can live.
Is it a place where you can live?
I don't think it's a place to live anymore.
It's beautiful, huh?
I want to be more beautifully, but more beautiful than anything.
You can continue to drink on the workday of the store because it's small.
On the day of the day, I will continue to enjoy beautiful morning and night.
On the day of the day of the day?
I'm sure you will paint the petal on the road on Almajiro.
Let's go!
What's that?
The promise to make it is not enough for you to find it.
Yes, I got it.
Let's go!
Ah! Ah! This shop!
It's a big deal for you.
Hurry up!
Wait!
Ah, it's gone.
I'm not going to play with the chair.
I was happy to play with Ryukku.
No! No!
No!
I can't give up!
Ah!
That's the old town hall.
Oh, no!
It's you!
Jiyakku!
We're going to play with you.
Ah! That guy...
Let's go!
We're going to play with you.
I want to play with you.
If you don't want to play with you, then you will be flounder.
I'm going to play with you.
What should we do now?
We're going to play with you.
Who is it?
It's the real one.
Um...
Sorry.
Who is it?
Huh?
Is the wind coming in from somewhere?
No, it's not.
Um...
I...
I thought I would die now.
Me too.
It's fine.
I don't think so.
You're probably in a fate.
Go upwards!
Let's go!
Interesting.
I'm back.
This is the day when I get my married.
What the hell is this? Where's the princess?
The magic of Ijira is the princess of my town!
I'm just saying that!
I don't know if you're doing anything.
Who knows who the beautiful princess is!
Isn't she the one who knows the beauty of the lake?
But we have to know that we've brought the lake!
No!
What?
That voice!
It's the enemy!
Are you still coming?
I know!
Great!
No way!
I can't lose!
Stop it!
The ship is going to be here!
No way!
I can't lose!
Ok, me too!
I'll wait!
Me too!
aaaaaaaaah....
oh, what was that?
what was that?
did it move?
hey...
hey, what were you doing?
Yuuuuh!
Wait!
Hey!
Hey, where are you going?
At this time, I'm going to kill you!
Where are you going, Eki-san?
Eki-san?
Eh? What happened?
I love you! I love you!
Where are you going, Eki-san?
Leave it to me!
Eki-san?
What are you going to save?
Cute.
What?
I can't see.
I have to be more patient.
Don't do it!
I'm in trouble!
Stop!
I understand.
I'm...
Ehh!
I'm gonna say bye because I'm happy to see a good laugh.
Stop!
I'll draw you.
I want to live!
Ehh!
What was that?
Stop it!
You're making fun of me!
What?
I hate you!
Stop it!
What?
What was that?
It's so funny.
What are you doing?
Oh, it's good that you're doing a good job.
Hey, don't do this!
It's not good!
Ah, I can't go.
Huh? What are you doing?
It's not scary.
What are you doing?
I don't know why.
If this happens...
What?
Huh?
There's always something like that.
Why?
If there's something wrong, I'm going to play around.
Don't worry about it.
What the hell are you talking about?
Anyway, I like Ohime-sama.
Yeah.
Um, everyone.
I have something to listen to.
It's the voice of Ohime-sama.
Like this?
Yeah.
Huh? That's...
I don't like this anymore.
Ohime-sama!
I'm going to play around.
I don't know.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I'm going to play around.
Yeah.
I don't think I can do this.
I have a hearing aid to that voice.
Huh?
I don't want to do that.
Wait a minute!
Stop it!
Hey!
Who's going to play around today?
Stop it!
Is that Ohime-sama?
I can't do that.
Shinko!
Oh!
You were Shinko, didn't you?
Shinko?
What's that?
I heard your voice when I heard your voice.
I wanted to meet you, Shinko.
You were in this world, weren't you?
What are you saying?
My name is Almajiro Hime.
Shinko is not?
Oh!
Really?
That's all?
Nararabi's egg.
You're so beautiful.
Your egg's effect is so strong.
It's not that strong.
Hey, you're using telepathy?
That's why you're using UiBanchi's power.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were going to take Zobino's medicine.
That's good.
I didn't feel like I'd be able to go back to the rest of the world.
Even so, why did you say that you're going to be able to go to Mamahara?
Because you're a beautiful person, you're a wonderful Mamahara.
I know you're beautiful.
I told you I'm a great boy.
Yes, yes.
I'm a great boy.
You're a great girl.
Oh, you're a famous man.
Oh, hello.
What's your opinion, Porano?
Yes.
I'm a friend of the same generation.
Same.
It's a lot of different.
Yeah, it's a lot of different.
The genius man is a prooffer who bez it and is responsible for his power.
Is that so much fun?
The energy?
So!
Even though it's just a small amount of energy and could it be a power of power!
This is a bad way to think of it!
Get to that!
Ah, so you don't have to wait for me.
Thanks all your support
Hoyobai Hayobai Hayobai
There's always a place where you can sleep
I'm calling you, I'm waiting for you here
It's a strange thing
I'm the only one who can't say anything
It's a heart that's in the middle of the galaxy
It's so..
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
I like dancing!
Everyone is dancing!
I'm interested!
I can enjoy dancing!
I love La Joy!
MRT
Made from the show
near the time
I'm here today
I'm for the Beauty Street
Eventually, every shopping mall is a small street
To forget about the truth
And what did you put clay on?
It must have beenessa
This year's event
And the humble sundae
So
Ah, you stop
Next time!
열심히 on, and on, with the beauty
to Kevin Все
I hope you are healthy
Thank you for watching.